bananaguide.com 2007-10-11

# BananaGuide

BananaGuide.com  
Untangled Web Inc. 

Privacy Policy

What This Privacy Policy Covers 

This policy covers how BananaGuide treats personal information that BananaGuide collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name and email address.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BananaGuide does not own or control, including membership sites with which BananaGuide has an affiliate relationship.

Information Collection and Use

General

BananaGuide collects a valid email address when you register to comment on the BG Wire blog. We do not ask for any further identifiers beyond a username and password.

Like all websites, BananaGuide automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, BananaGuide cookie information, and the pages you request. 

BananaGuide may use information to customize the advertising and content you see and to improve our services.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

BananaGuide does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, with your explicit permission.

Cookies

BananaGuide may set and access BananaGuide cookies on your computer. 

Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

BananaGuide may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us throught our feedback form. 

**BG Home\- Site Reviews ** **-** **Movie Reviews  
** **Sex Surfing 101-** **BG Wire -** **Map** © 2000, 2005 Untangled Web Inc.
